<?xml version="1.0"?>
<catalog>
   <Gin id="bk101">
      <Country>England</Country>
      <title>Bloom London Dry</title>
      <Taste>Delightful citrus tones with a floral hint from the honeysuckle and chamomile.</Taste>
      <price>$70-75 US</price>
      <ABV>40 %</ABV>
      <Best_served>Bloom London Dry with ice, tonic water and strawberries.</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk102">
      <Country>Scotland</Country>
      <title>Brockmans</title>
      <Taste>Juniper, Blackberries, Blueberries, Coriander,
         Angelica Root, Orris Root, Cassia Bark, Liquorice, Orange peel, Lemon peel, Almond</Taste>
      <price>$75-85 US</price>
      <ABV>40 %</ABV>
      <Best_served>Brockmans with Ice,
         tonic water (or Ginger Ale in the summer), pink grapefruit peel and a few blueberries</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk103">
      <Country>England</Country>
      <title>Portobello Road No. 171</title>
      <Taste>Juniper, coriander seed, angelica root, orris root, lemon Peel,
         orange peel, liquorice root, gassia bark, nutmeg</Taste>
      <price>$70-80 US</price>
      <ABV>42 %</ABV>
      <Best_served>Portobello Road No. 171 with ice, tonic water and a slice of grapefruit</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk104">
      <Country>United States of America</Country>
      <title>Brooklyn Gin</title>
      <Taste>Juniper, angelica root, lemon peel, lime peel, orange peel, lavender</Taste>
      <price>$75-85 US</price>
      <ABV>40 %</ABV>
      <Best_served>Brooklyn Gin with ice, tonic water, sliced orange, lime, and some thyme.

Conclusion</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk105">
      <Country>England</Country>
      <title>Beefeater 24</title>
      <Taste>Juniper, Japanese Sencha, Chinese Green Tea, Grapefruit Peels, Lemon Peel, Almond,
         Seville Orange Peel, Coriander Seed, Orris Root, Liquorice Root, Angelica Root, Angelica Seed</Taste>
      <price>$70-80 US</price>
      <ABV>45</ABV>
      <Best_served>Beefeater 24 with ice, tonic water and a slice of grapefruit.</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk106">
      <Country>Scotland</Country>
      <title>Hendricks</title>
      <Taste>Juniper, orange peel, yarrow, chamomile, coriander,
         and infused with Bulgarian rose petals and cucumber</Taste>
      <price>$75-85 US</price>
      <ABV>44 %</ABV>
      <Best_served>Hendrick’s with ice, tonic water, plus a couple of slices of cucumber to garnish</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk107">
      <Country>England</Country>
      <title>Sipsmith London Dry</title>
      <Taste>Lemon peel, Seville orange peel, juniper berries, Madagascan cinnamon bark,
         Belgian angelica root, Bulgarian coriander seed,
         Chinese Cassia Bark, Italian Orris Root, Spanish Ground Almond, Spanish liquorice root</Taste>
      <price>$75-85 US</price>
      <ABV>41.6 %</ABV>
      <Best_served>ipsmith London Dry Gin with ice, tonic water, plus a slice of lime.</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk108">
      <Country>Scotland</Country>
      <title>Caorunn</title>
      <Taste>Juniper Berries, Cassia Bark, Lemon Peel, Coriander Seed, Angelica Root,
         Orange Peel, Rowan Berry, Bog Myrtle, Heather, Coul Blush Apple, Dandelion Leaf.</Taste>
      <price>$70-82 US</price>
      <ABV>41.8</ABV>
      <Best_served>Caorunn with ice, tonic water, and slices of red apple.</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk109">
      <Country>Germany(Black Forest)</Country>
      <title>Monkey 47</title>
      <Taste>Here we go…. Juniper, acacia, flag, pimento, almond, orange, pepper (4 types), blackberry, cardamom,
         cassia, cinnamon, , rose mallow, lemon verbena, cloves, coriander, cranberries, pomelo, cubeb, dog rose,
          elderflower, ginger, Grains of Paradise, spruce, hawthorn berries, sage, ambrette, honeysuckle, jasmine,
           kaffir lime, lavender, lemon, chamomile, lemon balm, lemongrass, licorice, bee balm, nutmeg, orris,
            rosehip, sloe, angelica root, acacia flowers, bramble, lingonberries.</Taste>
      <price>$75-85 US</price>
      <ABV>47 %</ABV>
      <Best_served>Monkey 47 with ice, and ginger ale
         (I don’t feel you need garnish due to the 47 botanicals!).</Best_served>
   </Gin>
   <Gin id="bk110">
      <Country>Scotland (originally Brazil)</Country>
      <title>Tanqueray No. Ten</title>
      <Taste>Made with fresh citrus fruits, plus chamomile flowers, and juniper, coriander, angelica, and licorice.</Taste>
      <price>$70-80 US</price>
      <ABV>41.1</ABV>
      <Best_served>Tanqueray No.Ten with ice, tonic water, plus a slice of grapefruit.</Best_served>
   </Gin>

</catalog>
